<messages>
  <intro5>Want your friends to know how you are feeling? Use the Smiles button at the bottom. Just click on the smiley that shows your current emotions best!</intro5>
  <locPark>Wow! Omg, clocks and new sweet battle 2 here!!!</locPark>
  <locHome>This is your place. Home, sweet home. Feels good, doesn’t it? That big wooden box is your wardrobe. All your clothes are kept there. You might wanna stay home for a while, but when you get sick and tired of these four walls and decide to stretch your legs, click on the teleport and you’ll find yourself in the downtown.</locHome>
  <intro11>If you get sick and tired of the noise and tumult around, you can always get teleported to your home. Just click on the “Home” icon.</intro11>
  <sitTable>If you are waiting for someone to come and bring you a drink, you’ll be sitting there empty-tabled for a looooooooong time. Self-service, buddy! Click on the table to open the “Stuff Catalog.” Pick the thing you want, its quantity and then press the “Buy” button. As simple as that!!!</sitTable>
  <locCafe>Isn’t it cool in here? You can mellow out at one of the tables or play the Coin Rain mini-game to get the adrenaline going. To start the game, click on it.</locCafe>
  <intro6>Let’s learn the nuts and bolts of the “Friends” button. With its help you can sort out the list of friends that you’ve made while playing this game. Pick a corresponding status (online – green, online in another city – blue, offline – red) to find the buddy you are looking for! By clicking on them you can invite them over to where you are. You can send them a personal message, too! That’s not the extent of it, though. There’s also a “Remove a friend” button and a button by pressing which you can open a new window with the chosen friend. PHEW!!! Done it!</intro6>
  <standOnTeleport>Stay still! Don’t move a muscle! If you want to teleport, you have to press that violet button!</standOnTeleport>
  <takeRope>Drilling it into your head again: if you want to pull the rope over, you need to click repeatedly on the illuminated arrow on your side.</takeRope>
  <intro10>Do you see colorful balls here and there? They are not just a part of the “décor”. You can repaint palm trees by clicking on them. Point your mouse at a palm tree and press the left mouse button to aim a paint ball the first time; then release the mouse button to aim it the second time.</intro10>
  <locAccShop>Ready to add some spice to your wardrobe? Get started coz that’s the right place to do it. Just open the “Stuff Catalog,”  pick the thing you want, choose its color, press the “Buy” button and… be a different man (sorry, girls – no offence:).</locAccShop>
  <intro3>Always be on top of things. Find out all the news (opening of new institutions or launch of new games) by reading our blog.</intro3>
  <toPick>What are you waiting for? Pick up the hay and take it to the cow before an evil nicho beats you and steals it!</toPick>
  <academy>Keep silence! This is the Academy, not a marketplace! Behind each door you will find the classroom, where you can study while playing.</academy>
  <locAcademy>Excuse me, young gentleman. Are you heading to that house of science? Try your best in studies!</locAcademy>
  <intro1>First I’m gonna explain all these buttons to you. If you don’t wanna listen to my babble, press “Next”. Starting to get cold feet at the sight of all these buttons and windows? Chill out!!! They are here to help you. All these buildings have been constructed to entertain you and will happily draw you into their embrace. In the left top part of the screen you will find an icon that shows the amount of money that you’ve got.</intro1>
  <loc0>Now you are at a Shops Square location. If you are still lost and don’t know what to do, repeating it again – Shops Square. Here you can find a Magic Shop (abracadabra!) and a Clothes Shop where you can drastically change your character’s appearance!</loc0>
  <locationRope>Now you are at a Rope Street location. Violet circles are teleports that will transfer you to the Sweet Battle Game – candy or pie? Wanna compete in dexterity? You and your buddy need to stand on different ends of the rope. Click on the arrow as fast as possible to pull the rope over to your side.</locationRope>
  <loc2>Can I help you? I know you want to figure everything out yourself, but please, let me help you on this one. You are located in Mission Street. Wondering what the mission is??? It’s all about help (my mission is accomplished :). Enter the Missions Agency and earn money by collaborative work with other chobots.</loc2>
  <loc3>This is Café Street. You might be thinking, “There must be a café somewhere here…YAY!!!”. Bingo! There it is with lots of fun in store for you. You can dance there, hang out with your friends, crack everyone up with funny cocktails and just have a blast! There’s also a game club where you can entertain yourself by playing games.</loc3>
  <locGames>It’s game time. Have fun by playing one of the five mini-games. To start a game, click on it.</locGames>
  <intro4>We don’t want you to feel lonely and cut off from the world. That’s why we placed a chat room at the bottom of the screen that you can use to touch base with other chobots. To make it even easier for you, we integrated a pictured chat into it. Pictures might help you write your messages.</intro4>
  <openWardrope>Time for a fashion show!!! Here you can try on clothes by dragging the thing you want onto yourself. Click “Take off everything” to take the clothes off. Click “Close” to close the wardrobe.</openWardrope>
  <locMissions>Here is our missions’ agency! Check it regularly for new missions!</locMissions>
  <locGraphity>OMG, could you believe it??? It’s true graffiti wall! What are you waiting for? Use the tool panel on left side to create a new underground masterpiece!</locGraphity>
  <locMagicShop>Pick-a-boo!! It’s me again! Wondering where you are and what to do? Let me tell ya. Here you can get various trick things. Just open the “Stuff Catalog,” pick the thing you want, its quantity and then press the “Buy” button.</locMagicShop>
  <locCinema>Here you are, check our Chollywood!</locCinema>
  <locHomeShop>Hey! By using cho energy chobots can upgrade their own houses themselves!!</locHomeShop>
  <intro0>Hi there, dude! I’m Snailchob!!! I’ll be showing you around and helping you learn the ropes here! If you don’t wanna see me anymore, tick “Can figure it out by myself”. Of course, I’ll get very offended, but will continue accompanying you if you press the “Tips” button. Ready? Steady? Let’s go then!</intro0>
  <locEco>Hi! Guess what?! This is the place where you can upgrade your house and buy your own pet!! Yahoo!</locEco>
  <loc5>Hello again! Long time no see! This is Space Port Square. What do you do here? Hmmm… let’s see. First take part in space races. That’ll give you an adrenaline rush. Then go to the telescope and enjoy the sparkling infinity of the night sky. That’ll slow down your heartbeat and get it back to normal. Sounds like a plan? Go for it! And don't forget to visit chobots cinema!</loc5>
  <intro12>Congrats!!! I might’ve bored you to death with my non-stop chatter (sorry, I had to get it over with). There’s an upside to it, though. Now you are familiar with all the buttons on the screen! From now on I’ll be giving you tips during the game itself!</intro12>
  <intro2>You can put all your presents and stuff into a backpack. So don’t sweat it! You won’t have to lug them around. If you want to have a look into your backpack, click on the “Backpack” icon in the right bottom corner of the screen. To use anything from the bag, just pick the necessary thing and press the “Use” button.</intro2>
  <locEcoShop>Can you smell it? Yeah, right, here you can construct and buy your pet! Go ahead!</locEcoShop>
  <intro9>We decided to stick to the “there are more ways than one to skin a cat” principle. Another way to get to other locations is by clicking on the edge of the map or on the arrow.</intro9>
  <takeBall>Don’t these palm trees seem dull and boring to you? Come on, roll up your sleeves and give them some color. Point your mouse at a palm tree and press the left mouse button to aim a paint ball the first time; then press the mouse button once again to aim it the second time.</takeBall>
  <fullBottle>The bottle is already full of milk. You need to take a bucket and put it on the conveyor.</fullBottle>
  <locationCinema>A big blue screen! Don’t forget that your video can be here! Just send it to our team.</locationCinema>
  <missionFarm>Here’s what you have to do. Your ultimate task is to collect three buckets of milk. Sounds like a piece of cake? Not that easy, in fact. You’ll have to sweat a bit first: dig the field, sow seeds, water the field, cut the grass and take it to the cow. Hey there! Don’t even think of having a breather. There’s more work down the road. After you have filled a bottle with milk, get a bucket and take it to the conveyor. To add even more things on your plate, during the game evil nichos will be trying to stand in your way. You can neutralize them with a gun. The end.</missionFarm>
  <toKill>This is a state-of-the-art weapon that doesn’t do harm to living things. Just approach the nicho, point your mouse at it, then press the left mouse button. BANG – and it’s gone!!!</toKill>
  <toWater>This is a watering can that you can water a newly seeded field with. Just click on a seeded lot.</toWater>
  <toDig>This is a tool for digging the field. Hey, let’s call it a spade. Just click on a vacant lot.</toDig>
  <toCut>This is a scythe that you can mow grass with. Just click on a grass lot.</toCut>
  <toSmoke>This is seed that you can sow a field with after digging it first. Just click on a cultivated lot.</toSmoke>
  <loc1>Isn’t the Space Quay breathtaking? That makes two of us. You can keep standing there rooted to one spot and admire the beauty around or go flex your muscles a bit. Wanna go for the latter? Good choice!!! Do you see the violet circles over there? They are teleports that will transfer you to the Garbage Collector Game – collect more garbage than the competitor’s team. You can play alone or with your buddies.</loc1>
  <intro7>Want your friends to know how you are feeling? Use the Smiles button at the bottom. Just click on the smiley that shows your current emotions best!</intro7>
  <intro8>To help you avoid roaming around or getting lost in the city, we placed a map here. You can unfold it to see where you are and where you want to go. Just click on the place you’d like to find yourself in to get teleported there.</intro8>
  <housesShop/>
</messages>