<messages>
  <caption>Choproff</caption>
  <npcName>Choproff</npcName>
  <wellcome>Hello! I am professor Choproff. We were researching the Earth so long, so we collected some interesting facts. And I’m here to put you some questions, to see if you know these facts or not</wellcome>
  <win>You won, this items are yours</win>
  <lost>I’m sorry, but maybe you haven’t tried enough. Try again!</lost>
  <questComplete>You’ve already completed this quest</questComplete>
  <questions>What is the name of the bird that can fly backwards:#it is Hummingbirdbirds can’t fly backwards, it’s impossibleonly dragons could fly backwards but they are all deadName an animal that can see behind itself without turning its head:dog and cat#rabbit and parrotonly Jellyfish can do soWhere do the flowers with the biggest blooms grow:on the Mars#in the tropical forestsin the flowerpotsWhat is the oldest animal:#tortoisemickey Mouse catWhat animal has the biggest eyes:scared mouse#squidowlWhat is the fastest bird on the Earth: #falconwhite Parrotred ParrotHow many continents do we have today on the Earth: the Earth doesn’t have any continent#620What does it mean Greek word Pangea: #entire earthhappy birthdaygood luckWhich is the Earth's only natural satellite: the Suna Chobot City#the Moon$Which is the reason of many craters on the Moon’s surface:#meteor crashesastronautschobots did themWhich is the only object in space that man has ever visited: #MoonMilky WayMarsThe Moon is covered with seas:full of syrup#without waterfull of cheeseThe Moon orbits the Earth:no, the Earth orbits the Moonthe Moon can’t orbit the Earth because it’s made of cheese#yes, it doesWhich side does the Polar Star point:eastwest#northHow many times does the Polar Star larger than the sun:#50100201Why did the Polar Star serve as a guide for travelers over millennia:#it doesn't change its location in the skyit’s the only star in the skyit looks nicePlant the Venus Flytrap catches and digests:#insects and spidersother  plantselephantsAre there any plants that can digest insects:no, there are only plants that can digest elephantsyes, but only in case there are no elephants#yes, they are called FlytrapsWe can find flying fish:in our dream onlyin fairy tale only#in all of the major oceansWhy does flying fish have ability to fly:#in order to escape from predatorsin order to see the sunin order to become a cosmonautWhen does the plant Flytrap close the trap:when it goes to bed#when an insect comes into contact with one or more of the hairs on the leaveswhen it’s not hungry any moreWhen does the plant Flytrap resume hunting:#only after it has digested its previous preyeach Fridayplants don’t huntThe flying fish can:make pancakes#make short gliding flights through air, above the surface of the waterdanceThe human organism by 65% consists of:bonescookies#waterWhose organism contains has higher percentage of the water:the old man’sa driver’s#a baby’sIt is essential for people to have access to:#clean fresh waterto sweetsto Chobots worldWhich is the fastest land animal on Earth that can speed up to 70 mph:no animal can run that fast#cheetahscared turtlePeregrine Falcon can reach speeds of over 270 mph when:running#flying downwardsit flies in the planeThe gigantic squid's eyes are larger than:#The eyes of any other animal that has ever existed on EarthA soccer field the Squids don’t have eyesWho created the first hot air balloon:Harry Potter#Montgolfier brothersScrooge McDuckThe air balloon created by Montgolfier brothers was filled with:WaterFog#Hot airMontgolfier brothers created:#The first hot air balloonA trampolineChobots The first manned flight ever was made in:#a hot air balloona cold air balloona trainWhat does enable a flying fish to take short gliding flights through air: engine#pectoral finswingsOn people's dirty skin are accumulated:mushrooms#various germs and bacteriacoinsVarious germs and bacteria are accumulated on:the Suna soap#people's dirty skinWhich is the coldest, windiest, highest and driest continent on Earth:Africa#AntarcticaMarsPeople in Antarctica have to breathe through special masks because:the fresh air stinksthere is a carnival all the year round#it’s very cold thereA giant sequoia’s stem thickness is nearly 10:#meterscentimeterskilogram Which is the smallest bird on Earth (adults weigh 2 grams or 0.07ounces):ostrich#hummingbirdmosquito The biggest flower blooms are on:#a plant called Rafflesiaa fir treea coconut treeThe flower Rafflesia has the biggest:car#bloomsambitionHow does an ant act when it’s intoxicated:it sings#it falls over on its right sideit asks stupid questionsCan an ant lift an elephant:yes, it canonly if it knows Chuck Norris in person#no, it can lift only 50 times its own weightArmadillo eats only:hamburgers#insectsfrench cheese dor bleuArmadillo has:#100 teeth5 legs2 cars and 1 villa in MiamiWhat is a size of blue whale’s heart:a size of a big house#a size of a small cara size of a mouseIs a blue whale the largest creature that has ever lived on earth:no, dinosaurs were bigger than blue whales, weren’t they?#yes, it isnext question pleaseA sheep have four chambers stomach because:#it helps them to digest the foodsheep are big fans of ALFonly Chopix knows the answerHow many chambers do the ships have:the ships don’t have stomachno one ever counted#four A Great White Shark inhabits:the woodsthe Internet#the oceansWho is more dangerous:an anta moderator#a great white sharkBlackspot angelfish can change from female to male:when there is a president election in the US#not by simply wishing, the change happens for a specific reasonwith the help of sith dark side powerIs the sun a big star:yes, it is huge star and has a enough energy to power 5604 houses #no, It is actually a very small staryes, it is a very big TV star. It has it’s own TV showSun is made of:honeypure CHO energy#it is made up of hot gassesHow old is the sun:nobody except Vayerman knows it#about 4.5 million years oldit shouldn’t be very old, it doesn’t look like an old star, maybe 100 years?How long the sun will exist:the sun will exist foreveri don’t care.#sun will continue to be in existence for 5 million more yearsCockroaches can live for a month without:#foodthey don’t live that longparties What cockroaches can hold for 45 minutes:their money#their breathhot potatoThe cockroaches can slow down:#their heart ratethe falling of Dow Jones IndexONLY COCKROACHES CAN SLOW DOWN CHUCK NORRISDo the cockroaches withstand radiation better than humans:#yes, they doyes, only if they wear special anti-rad costume hah! Of course noWind carries over 100 million tons of sand grains around the Earth:per hour#per yeareach time you say “can I become a moderator?”.Does Armadillo has more teeth than any other land mammal:No#YesWho?Blue whale weight is equal to:#22 elephants2 airplanes with elephants and 1 airplane without elephants12 chobots after they ate a giant pillThe oldest living thing on Earth is:dinosaur #the flowering shrubs called Creosote Bushesmaster JodaCreosote Bushes can be located:#in the Mojave Desertin Tinagothic chobot-house on 2nd floor behind the furniturein some craters of the MoonHow old can be Creosote Bushes:nobody knows#11000 years oldhow should I know this?Who are the largest and strongest of living birds:penguinshummingbird#ostrichesWhat is the height of ostriches:1 m 29 cm and 33 mm#2.4m(about 8 ft)The height of Ostriches is equal to their width multiplied by 2 What is the weight of Ostriches:#their weight is up to 136 kg(300 lb)their maximum weight is 50 kgtheir weight is 250 kg when they feel happy and 222 kg when they are depressedMale ostriches are:sad#black with white wings and tailwhat do I do here?Ostriches are:my neighbors#rapid runnersI like cookiesOstriches can attain speed :about 300 km/s after they have used a speed magic#about 65 km/h (40 mph)about 10 mphWeight of ostriches’ eggs is:100 kg there is no right answer. Please ask next question.#1.4 kg (about 3 lb)When does father ostrich take care about the eggs: the male sings all the night and female make some spaghetti during the day.#the male sits on eggs at night, and the female incubates them by daythe male ostriches think about peace in whole world and female about how to produce more eggs during the day.What is the name of the highest trees:money trees#giant sequoiaschristmas treesThe highest trees Giant sequoias are up to:100 meters wide!233*40/0.003 + sin60 – arctg2#100 meters highWhat is the brightest thing in the sky:an airplane#the Sunthe MoonWhat is the Sun:electric lampinhabited planet#small starGiant sequoia’s height is more than:#60 adult man’s heightheight of 2 Titanicsheight of 1 Eiffel tower</questions>
</messages>