<messages>
  <afterBuyWarning>After this purchase you will have {0} coins on your account. Want to buy?</afterBuyWarning>
  <bagIsFull>Your bag is full! Sorry but you can't buy this.</bagIsFull>
  <buy>Buy</buy>
  <comingSoon>Coming soon</comingSoon>
  <magicBalls>Having balloons is fun. Having a ball to play with is much more fun.</magicBalls>
  <magicBevel>Do you want to feel power of cho?</magicBevel>
  <magicBlend>Spy mode is on!</magicBlend>
  <magicBlur>Wanna feel what it’s like to be a ghost? Take a bite of this candy and you are gone, into thin air. 
  Helloooooo? Where are you? Can’t see ya.</magicBlur>
  <magicBottle>One drop of this elixir and you are in the limelight. Isn’t it something you’ve been dreaming of?</magicBottle>
  <magicBubble>It’s high time to have a holiday. WOOHOO!!! Try this one and a balloon will pop up in your hands 
  to get your holiday off to a good start.</magicBubble>
  <magicBubbleBlue>Two balloons are better than one, right? What are you waiting for then? Wolf it down!!!</magicBubbleBlue>
  <magicBubbleYellow>Three balloons are better than two!</magicBubbleYellow>
  <magicCharly>Have you ever seen Charlie Chaplin’s films? Yeah, that black and white fun!</magicCharly>
  <magicFlame>Carefully, you can hurt yourself with this sweet!</magicFlame>
  <magicGhost>One shadow left.</magicGhost>
  <magicHue>Disco 80s? Yeah, keep rolling!</magicHue>
  <magicInvert>Black hole – what is it?</magicInvert>
  <magicLarge>Tell me most popular giant! Yep, that’s right – Gulliver! Want to try?</magicLarge>
  <magicNearest>Spread the magic</magicNearest>
  <magicPromotion>Promotion</magicPromotion>
  <magicScale>Get an ant’s perspective of the world!</magicScale>
  <magicSpeed>Wanna run at lightning speed? Eat this candy. Come on! Shovel it down!</magicSpeed>
  <magicStar>As you might already be in the limelight, why not get a star above your head?</magicStar>
  <magicTeleport>Teleport</magicTeleport>
  <magicToxic>OMG, have you ever visited Chernobyl before?</magicToxic>
  <magicUmnik>Hey, wanna feel big brains in your head?</magicUmnik>
  <magicZhurdyai>100 hamburgers inside!</magicZhurdyai>
  <magic_buben>Real Rain</magic_buben>
  <magic_lightning>Lightning</magic_lightning>
  <magic_rainbow>Rainbow</magic_rainbow>
  <magic_snow>Snow</magic_snow>
  <moonWalk>MoonWalk</moonWalk>
  <notEnoughMoney>You don't have enough money to buy this.</notEnoughMoney>
  <null/>
</messages>