<messages>
  <paymentExplanationText2>After you click the Buy Now button, you will be redirected to payment system. Pop Up Window will open. Make sure that your browser is not blocking it</paymentExplanationText2>
  <comingSoonDescription>Be on top of things! From week to week citizens get more opportunities, exclusive clothing, and new features. You’ll be surprised with each update made in Chobots.</comingSoonDescription>
  <citizenshipDescription>Citizenship is your pass to the world of more creativity, greater fun and unforgettable experience. Stop being just a tourist on a sightseeing trip in Chobots world. Get your citizen passport to see so many more opportunities open up for you: decorating your house, walking your pet, doing citizens’ magic, creating graffiti drawings!!Explore Chobots inside and out</citizenshipDescription>
  <citizenship>Citizenship!</citizenship>
  <comingSoon>Coming Soon!</comingSoon>
  <creativity>Creativity!</creativity>
  <creativityDescription>Develop your creativity with Chobots!- create your own style with   clothes from citizens’ catalogue- make art on graffiti wall- build your house and furnish it- construct a pet and let others see it</creativityDescription>
  <experienceDescription>Experience the popularity. Do you want to stay out of the crowd? Distinguish yourself from the others with:- bigger chat bubble- amazing suits and clothing- your graffiti drawings- ability to walk your pet</experienceDescription>
  <experience>Experience!</experience>
  <fun>Fun!</fun>
  <funDescription>Get more fun out of the citizens’ world!- amaze everyone with citizens’ magic- get more features for your pets - get twice more money - give parties in your big house- have an access to the games from your   house- be able to enter a full city - wear animal mask or any other funny costume</funDescription>
  <paymentExplanationText1>Please ask your parents  to buy Chobots Citizenship. We accept payments in all currencies. A current exchange rate of your bank will be used when withdrawing the money.</paymentExplanationText1>
</messages>