<messages>
	<item>What do you call people who are afraid of Santa Claus? Claustrophobic</item>
	<item>The shortest distance between two points is under construction</item>
	<item>The fact that no one understands you doesn't make you an artist</item>
	<item>Luck never made a man wise</item>
	<item>Go and wake up your luck</item>
	<item>If you can dream it, you can do it</item>
	<item>Happiness is a warm puppy</item>
	<item>Winners never quit and quitters never win</item>
	<item>Moo, I'm a horse</item>
	<item>I wish I could talk...</item>
	<item>2+2 = Fish, right?</item>
	<item>If you put your mind to it, you can achieve anything</item>
	<item>Hello! Hello!</item>
	<item>1+1 is window!!</item>
	<item>Oppa gangnam style!</item>
	<item>Feed me...</item>
	<item>Imagine being a freak like me. Oh wait...</item>
	<item>If I count to 5, will you run away and hide... forever?</item>
	<item>Help! My owner doesn't feed me!</item>
	<item>I want pie...</item>
	<item>The road to success... is always under construction</item>
	<item>Why don't I ever grow up?</item>
	<item>I love my owner!</item>
	<item>Expecto Patronum!</item>
	<item>I speak in French when you're not looking.</item>
	<item>Bonjour! Comment ca va?</item>
	<item>You are what you eat, right? Time to eat a mod!</item>
	<item>This sentence is false</item>
	<item>What happens if I pop your chat bubble?</item>
	<item>Just nod and pretend you understand</item>
	<item>May the best person win, unless it's you</item>
	<item>I forgot to feed my owner last night</item>
	<item>Why did the chicken cross the road?</item>
	<item>Did you know that jellyfish?</item>
	<item>Why do feet smell and noses run?</item>
	<item>#YOLO</item>
	<item>How is my beard coming along?</item>
	<item>Why can't I be a citizen?</item>
	<item>Opportunity called. Turns out it was the wrong number.</item>
	<item>When I said I couldn't pay the doctor, he gave me another month to live!</item>
	<item>Smile!</item>
	<item>Let's play a game!</item>
	<item>Let's go visit our friends!</item>
	<item>Why are Chobots so smelly?</item>
	<item>Can I have a pet?</item>
	<item>Meow</item>
	<item>Do you like sweet battle?</item>
	<item>Help! I can't find my owner!</item>
	<item>Can you dance for me?</item>
	<item>Draw me like one of your French pets</item>
	<item>Live and love.</item>
	<item>Never, ever, give up.</item>
	<item>I'm going to host a party with three people: me, myself, and I</item>
	<item>To the world you might just be one person, but to one person you might be the world</item>
	<item>The key to life is imagination. If you don't have that, no matter what you have, it's meaningless. If you do have imagination.. you can make a feast of straw</item>
	<item>If someone can't do something, then why should I?</item>
	<item>Wanna play soccer?</item>
	<item>You mad cho?</item>
	<item>I'm a beautiful man flower waiting to blossom!</item>
	<item>I am part Nicho if you ask my friends.</item>
	<item>You, my friend, are from a different planet all together.</item>
	<item>Dr! Dr! Where's Dr Chogreen!?</item>
	<item>What letter is the one after 3?</item>
	<item>Run along</item>
	<item>My life needs editing...</item>
	<item>Just cut to the chase</item>
	<item>Another one bites the dust</item>
	<item>A day without sunshine is like, you know, night.</item>
	<item>Roses are red.. And pink, purple, yellow, and white. </item>
	<item>My owner is psycho! Help me!</item>
	<item>Ew. Don't touch me.</item>
	<item>Don't be sad because I'm better than you</item>
	<item>It's hard living on my own...</item>
	<item>As they said at the pound, pet food each day keeps me from running away. Feed me please!</item>
	<item>Where's the rain? I want rain!</item>
	<item>Do I really have to ask you again?</item>
	<item>I was just going to say hi!</item>
	<item>Let's go to the Cafe and have some coffee together!</item>
	<item>Draw something for me!</item>
	<item>9 PM... it's time to go to bed!</item>
	<item>I need new shoes. Buy me new shoes please?</item>
	<item>Where does all this magic come from? Is it Harry Potter or what?</item>
	<item>Who ate my hot dog?</item>
	<item>What happened to skittles these days?</item>
	<item>I'm sure if I don't get fed, I'm just going to end up like Shrek.</item>
	<item>Please don't buy food from the cafe... I can't tell the difference between Horse and Cow!</item>
	<item>Being lazy and being tired are two completely different things.</item>
	<item>I work at home. It's called home-work.</item>
	<item>They say you only live once... so what are cats supposed to say?</item>
	<item>It's my birthday!</item>
	<item>Knock knock, Whos there? Orange. Orange who? Orange you glad I didn't say banana?</item>
	<item>Butterflies can't see their wings. They can't see how truly beautiful they are, but everyone else can. People are like that as well.</item>
	<item>Well begun is half done</item>
	<item>What we see depends mainly on what we look for</item>
	<item>Don't postpone joy</item>
	<item>Be yourself</item>
	<item>Freedom is never free</item>
	<item>Come on, let's play!</item>
	<item>Always remember you're unique, just like everyone else</item>
	<item>Please do not feed the pets. If you have any suitable food, give it to the moderator on duty</item>
	<item>Press any key... no, no, no, NOT THAT ONE!</item>
	<item>A closed mouth gathers no foot</item>
	<item>Never stand between a dog and the hydrant</item>
	<item>Age is of no importance unless you're a cheese</item>
	<item>I was born intelligent - education ruined me</item>
	<item>There is an exception to every rule, except this one</item>
	<item>Practice makes perfect...But nobody's perfect...so why practice?</item>
	<item>How come "abbreviated" is such a long word?</item>
	<item>Good decision</item>
	<item>Power corrupts</item>
	<item>A fool's paradise</item>
	<item>Here I am! What were your other 2 wishes?</item>
	<item>I'm not perfect but I'm so close it's scary...</item>
	<item>Flying is simple. You just throw yourself at the ground and miss</item>
	<item>I don't like to repeat things, so listen carefully the first six times</item>
	<item>Any connection between your reality and mine is purely coincidental</item>
	<item>I'll try being nicer if you'll try being smarter</item>
	<item>Who? Me?</item>
	<item>I'm just wandering from hire to there</item>
	<item>I have plenty of talent and vision. I just don't care</item>
	<item>I'm out of my mind, but feel free to leave a message</item>
	<item>Allow me to introduce my selves</item>
	<item>You!... Off my planet!</item>
	<item>Whatever you say!</item>
	<item>brb</item>
	<item>Bye-Bye</item>
	<item>See you later!</item>
	<item>Have a nice day</item>
	<item>How are you doing?</item>
	<item>Do you speak Spanish?</item>
	<item>I'm still here</item>
	<item>How do you spell your name?</item>
	<item>Congratulations!</item>
	<item>I doubt whether that's true</item>
	<item>Born free. Taxed to death</item>
	<item>How do you do?</item>
	<item>What's up?</item>
	<item>What is happening here?</item>
	<item>Feeling wonderful</item>
	<item>Little sleepy</item>
	<item>Little tired</item>
	<item>Let's go to the cinema!</item>
	<item>Awesome movie!</item>
	<item>I'm hungry!</item>
	<item>Can i have some sweets?</item>
	<item>Great!</item>
	<item>Let's play the ball!</item>
	<item>Let's have a break</item>
	<item>The reason honey is so easy to digest is that it's already been digested by a bee</item>
	<item>Roosters cannot crow if they cannot extend their necks</item>
	<item>The color blue has a calming effect</item>
	<item>Bats always turn left when exiting a cave</item>
	<item>Dalmatians are born without spots</item>
	<item>Chewing gum while peeling onions will keep you from crying</item>
	<item>What about going to the gamezone?</item>
	<item>I like to watch you playing Choboard!</item>
	<item>Let's go to the cafe street and meet our friends!</item>
	<item>Let's visit somebody's home</item>
	<item>Don't you like playing sliders?</item>
	<item>A crocodile can't stick it's tongue out</item>
	<item>A duck's quack doesn't echo, and no one knows why</item>
	<item>Like fingerprints, everyone's tongue print is different</item>
	<item>Hot water is heavier than cold</item>
	<item>Gorillas sleep as much as fourteen hours per day</item>
	<item>Dolphins sleep with one eye open!</item>
	<item>Would a fly without wings be called a walk?</item>
	<item>Research is what you are doing when you don't know what you are doing</item>
	<item>Is a sleeping bag a nap sack?</item>
	<item>Is a man full of wonder a wonderful man?</item>
	<item>What's another word for synonym?</item>
	<item>People say nothing is impossible, but I do nothing every day</item>
	<item>63% of pet owners sleep with their pets</item>
	<item>58% of school kids say pizza is their favorite cafeteria food</item>
	<item>One in three dog owners say they have talked to their pets on the phone</item>
	<item>One in seven Americans can't locate the U.S. on a map</item>
	<item>When you sneeze, all your bodily functions stop, even your heart</item>
	<item>I am so clever that sometimes I don't understand a single word of what I am saying</item>
	<item>I like to move it, move it</item>
	<item>push the button</item>
	<item>I'm ok!</item>
	<item>Play!Play!Play!</item>
	<item>No act of kindness, no matter how small, is ever wasted</item>
	<item>To have a good friend is one of the greatest delights of life</item>
	<item>Happiness is an unexpected hug</item>
	<item>To the world you may be just one person. but to one person you may be the world</item>
	<item>To have joy one must share it</item>
	<item>It is your friends who make your world</item>
	<item>If at first you don't succeed skydiving is not for you</item>
	<item>Doing homework is a drag</item>
	<item>The pen is mightier than the sword</item>
	<item>Good advice is beyond price</item>
	<item>Live and learn</item>
	<item>Too much knowledge makes the head bald</item>
	<item>Knowledge is power</item>
	<item>Live and let live</item>
	<item>Great deeds live</item>
	<item>A sound mind in a sound body</item>
	<item>Dry feet, warm head bring safe to bed</item>
	<item>Wit is better than wealth</item>
	<item>Handsome is as handsome does</item>
	<item>A friend's eye is a good mirror</item>
	<item>A wise man changes his mind, a fool never will</item>
	<item>There is a great force in soft command</item>
	<item>A merry heart is a good medicine</item>
	<item>Cheek brings Success</item>
	<item>Rome was not built in a day</item>
	<item>Calamity is a man's true touchstone</item>
	<item>Little and sweet</item>
	<item>A good name will sell itself</item>
	<item>No legacy so rich as honesty</item>
	<item>A clean hand wants no washing</item>
	<item>Avoid evil and it will avoid you</item>
	<item>Return good for evil</item>
	<item>Pride goes before a fall</item>
	<item>I'm planning to be more spontaneous in the future</item>
	<item>I know Karate, Kung Fu, and 47 other dangerous words...</item>
	<item>An unbreakable toy is useful for breaking other toys</item>
	<item>Keep smiling, it makes people wonder what you're up to</item>
	<item>Procrastinate now, don't put it off</item>
	<item>Borrow money from pessimists - they don't expect it back</item>
	<item>42.7% of all statistics are made up on the spot</item>
	<item>A clear conscience is usually the sign of a bad memory</item>
	<item>OK, so what's the speed of dark?</item>
	<item>Depression is merely anger without enthusiasm</item>
	<item>Ambition is a poor excuse for not having enough sense to be lazy</item>
	<item>Hard work pays off in the future, laziness pays off now</item>
	<item>I intend to live forever -- so far, so good</item>
	<item>If at first you don't succeed, destroy all evidence that you tried</item>
	<item>I didn't lose my mind, I sold it on e-bay</item>
	<item>The Earth Is Full - Go Home</item>
	<item>Don't regret doing things, regret getting caught</item>
	<item>Is tuna really Chicken?</item>
	<item>I did my homework! I just forgot to write it down</item>
	<item>Thank you for visiting reality, come again</item>
	<item>I can see clearly now, the brain is gone</item>
	<item>Ever stop to think, and forget to start again?</item>
	<item>A conclusion is simply the place where you got tired of thinking</item>
	<item>Don't be so open-minded your brains fall out</item>
	<item>Computers are not intelligent. They only think they are</item>
	<item>Press any key to continue or any other key to quit...</item>
	<item>If at first you don't succeed skydiving is not for you</item>
	<item>Every morning is the dawn of a new error...</item>
	<item>If one synchronized swimmer drowns, do the rest have to drown too?</item>
	<item>If things get any worse, I'll have to ask you to stop helping me</item>
	<item>Car service: If it ain't broke, we'll break it</item>
	<item>Shin: A device for finding furniture in the dark</item>
	<item>Computers make very fast, very accurate mistakes</item>
	<item>My software never has bugs. It just develops random features</item>
	<item>Disinformation is not as good as datinformation</item>
	<item>I like chobots, but I don't think I could eat a whole one</item>
	<item>I know Karate, Kung Fu, and 47 other dangerous words...</item>
	<item>Why did the tomato turn red? Because it saw the salad dressing!</item>
	<item>Never trust an atom, they make up everything</item>
	<item>I'm not arguing, I'm just explaining why I'm right</item>
	<item>Life is short, smile while you still have teeth</item>
	<item>Don't worry if plan A fails, there are 25 more letters in the alphabet</item>
	<item>Why do they call it rush hour when nothing moves?</item>
	<item>Reality is just a crutch for people who can't handle science fiction</item>
	<item>Why is it called a "drive-through" if you have to stop?</item>
	<item>Asking a writer what he thinks about criticism is like asking a lamppost what it thinks about dogs</item>
	<item>Why do we park in a driveway and drive in a parkway?</item>
	<item>Don't drink and drive, you might hit a bump and spill your drink</item>
	<item>The universe is made of protons, neutrons, electrons and morons</item>
	<item>I'm not lazy, I'm just conserving energy</item>
	<item>Life is too short to be serious all the time. So, if you can't laugh at yourself, call me, I'll laugh at you</item>
	<item>Why don't scientists trust atoms? Because they make up everything</item>
	<item>Why did the hipster burn his tongue? Because he drank his coffee before it was cool</item>
	<item>I'm not arguing, I'm just explaining why I'm right</item>
	<item>Why did the chicken cross the playground? To get to the other slide</item>
	<item>Why can't you trust an atom? Because they make up everything!</item>
	<item>Why did the scarecrow win an award? Because he was outstanding in his field</item>
	<item>I'm not arguing, I'm just explaining why I'm right</item>
	<item>Why did the banana go to the doctor? Because it wasn't peeling well</item>
	<item>Why don't scientists trust atoms? Because they make up everything</item>
	<item>Why did the coffee file a police report? Because it was mugged</item>
	<item>Why did the tomato turn green? Because it saw the salad dressing</item>
	<item>Life is too short to waste time on things that don't make you happy</item>
	<item>Never stop dreaming</item>
	<item>Always look on the bright side of life</item>
	<item>The early bird catches the worm</item>
	<item>Time flies when you're having fun</item>
	<item>Actions speak louder than words</item>
	<item>Don't judge a book by its cover</item>
	<item>Every cloud has a silver lining</item>
	<item>Patience is a virtue</item>
	<item>Laughter is the best medicine</item>
	<item>Good things come to those who wait</item>
	<item>Where there's a will, there's a way</item>
	<item>Keep calm and carry on</item>
	<item>Live every day as if it were your last</item>
	<item>The grass is always greener on the other side</item>
	<item>Love conquers all</item>
	<item>You miss 100% of the shots you don't take</item>
	<item>Never give up on your dreams</item>
	<item>Life is a journey, not a destination</item>
	<item>It's not about the destination, it's about the journey</item>
	<item>Believe in yourself and all that you are. Know that there is something inside you that is greater than any obstacle</item>
	<item>Be the change you wish to see in the world</item>
	<item>Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts</item>
	<item>The only way to do great work is to love what you do</item>
	<item>Be yourself, everyone else is already taken</item>
	<item>Life is 10% what happens to you and 90% how you react to it</item>
	<item>Everything you can imagine is real</item>
	<item>Be the reason someone smiles today</item>
	<item>Life is like a camera, focus on the good times, develop from the negatives, and if things don't work out, take another shot</item>
	<item>It always seems impossible until it's done</item>
	<item>Don't cry because it's over, smile because it happened</item>
	<item>You are never too old to set another goal or to dream a new dream</item>
	<item>Don't let yesterday take up too much of today</item>
	<item>The best way to predict the future is to create it</item>
	<item>If you want to achieve greatness, stop asking for permission</item>
	<item>You can't go back and change the beginning, but you can start where you are and change the ending</item>
	<item>The difference between ordinary and extraordinary is that little extra</item>
	<item>Life is short, make it sweet</item>
	<item>It's not what you look at that matters, it's what you see</item>
	<item>Life is not a problem to be solved, but a reality to be experienced</item>
	<item>Believe you can and you're halfway there</item>
	<item>You don't have to be great to start, but you have to start to be great</item>
	<item>Chase your dreams, not your fears</item>
</messages>