<messages>	<item>What do you call people who are afraid of Santa Claus? Claustrophobic</item>	<item>The shortest distance between two points is under construction</item>	<item>The fact that no one understands you doesn't make you an artist</item>	<item>Luck never made a man wise</item>	<item>Go and wake up your luck</item>	<item>If you can dream it, you can do it</item>	<item>Happiness is a warm puppy</item>	<item>Well begun is half done</item>	<item>What we see depends mainly on what we look for</item>	<item>Don't postpone joy</item>	<item>Be yourself</item>	<item>Freedom is never free</item>	<item>Come on, let's play!</item>	<item>Always remember you're unique, just like everyone else</item>	<item>Please do not feed the pets. If you have any suitable food, give it to the moderator on duty</item>	<item>Press any key... no, no, no, NOT THAT ONE!</item>	<item>A closed mouth gathers no foot</item>	<item>Never stand between a dog and the hydrant</item>	<item>Age is of no importance unless you're a cheese</item>	<item>I was born intelligent - education ruined me</item>	<item>There is an exception to every rule, except this one</item>	<item>Practice makes perfect...But nobody's perfect...so why practice?</item>	<item>How come "abbreviated" is such a long word?</item>	<item>Good decision</item>	<item>Power corrupts</item>	<item>A fool's paradise</item>	<item>Here I am! What were your other 2 wishes?</item>	<item>I'm not perfect but I'm so close it's scary...</item>	<item>Flying is simple. You just throw yourself at the ground and miss</item>	<item>I don't like to repeat things, so listen carefully the first six times</item>	<item>Any connection between your reality and mine is purely coincidental</item>	<item>I'll try being nicer if you'll try being smarter</item>	<item>Who? Me?</item>	<item>I'm just wandering from hire to there</item>	<item>I have plenty of talent and vision. I just don't care</item>	<item>I'm out of my mind, but feel free to leave a message</item>	<item>Allow me to introduce my selves</item>	<item>You!... Off my planet!</item>	<item>Whatever you say!</item>	<item>brb</item>	<item>Bye-Bye</item>	<item>See you later!</item>	<item>Have a nice day</item>	<item>How are you doing?</item>	<item>Do you speak Spanish?</item>	<item>I'm still here</item>	<item>How do you spell your name?</item>	<item>Congratulations!</item>	<item>I doubt whether that's true</item>	<item>Born free. Taxed to death</item>	<item>How do you do?</item>	<item>What's up?</item>	<item>What is happening here?</item>	<item>Feeling wonderful</item>	<item>Little sleepy</item>	<item>Little tired</item>	<item>Let's go to the cinema!</item>	<item>Awesome movie!</item>	<item>I'm hungry!</item>	<item>Can i have some sweets?</item>	<item>Great!</item>	<item>Let's play the ball!</item>	<item>Let's have a break</item>	<item>The reason honey is so easy to digest is that it's already been digested by a bee</item>	<item>Roosters cannot crow if they cannot extend their necks</item>	<item>The color blue has a calming effect</item>	<item>Bats always turn left when exiting a cave</item>	<item>Dalmatians are born without spots</item>	<item>Chewing gum while peeling onions will keep you from crying</item>	<item>What about going to the gamezone?</item>	<item>I like to watch you playing Choboard!</item>	<item>Let's go to the cafe street and meet our friends!</item>	<item>Let's visit somebody's home</item>	<item>Don't you like playing sliders?</item>	<item>A crocodile can't stick it's tongue out</item>	<item>A duck's quack doesn't echo, and no one knows why</item>	<item>Like fingerprints, everyone's tongue print is different</item>	<item>Hot water is heavier than cold</item>	<item>Gorillas sleep as much as fourteen hours per day</item>	<item>Dolphins sleep with one eye open!</item>	<item>Would a fly without wings be called a walk?</item>	<item>Research is what you are doing when you don't know what you are doing</item>	<item>Is a sleeping bag a nap sack?</item>	<item>Is a man full of wonder a wonderful man?</item>	<item>What's another word for synonym?</item>	<item>People say nothing is impossible, but I do nothing every day</item>	<item>Where were we?</item>	<item>That is a good idea</item>	<item>Let us hope for the best</item>	<item>Things happen</item>	<item>Next time lucky</item>	<item>Don't be late, please!</item>	<item>I can't believe it!</item>	<item>Watch out!</item>	<item>Who knows!</item>	<item>And so on and so forth</item>	<item>As sure as eggs is eggs</item>	<item>I am afraid you are wrong</item>	<item>I was not attending</item>	<item>What do you mean by saying it?</item>	<item>Not to know is bad, not to wish to know is worse</item>	<item>Success doesn't come to you, you go to it</item>	<item>Everything takes longer than you think</item>	<item>If you want to be somebody, somebody really special, be yourself!</item>	<item>A good match blows fire...</item>	<item>I didn't do it!</item>	<item>Operator! Give me the number for 911!</item>	<item>Just because I don't care doesn't mean I don't understand</item>	<item>'To Start Press Any Key'. Where's the ANY key?</item>	<item>Curiosity killed the cat!</item>	<item>Mmm... Muffins...</item>	<item>When pigs fly!</item>	<item>Live and learn!</item>	<item>Nothing venture, nothing have</item>	<item>Don't worry. I forgot your name too</item>	<item>Any time!</item>	<item>Don't even think about it!</item>	<item>Ahhh...I see the screw up fairy has visited us again</item>	<item>How about never? Is never good for you?</item>	<item>It sounds like English, but I can't understand a word you're saying</item>	<item>No, my powers can only be used for good</item>	<item>Are you a mind reader? I better think a little quieter next time...</item>	<item>Imagine this: I will win and you will lose. Do we need to go on?</item>	<item>If I throw a stick, will you leave?</item>	<item>My toys! My toys! I can't do this job without my toys!</item>	<item>LOL!!!</item>	<item>WOOT!</item>	<item>Believe in yourself</item>	<item>Hi, dude!!</item>	<item>Let's rock it!</item>	<item>Doh!</item>	<item>It's time to paint the town red!</item>	<item>Don't leave me along.</item>	<item>I can fly ))</item>	<item>Wohoo! life is good!</item>	<item>Hugs and kisses</item>	<item>Did I miss something?</item>	<item>I want more</item>	<item>Once again?</item>	<item>It's so exciting!</item>	<item>I feel that today is your lucky day</item>	<item>Let's earn some bugs</item>	<item>Hurray!!</item>	<item>I can wait to see your win</item>	<item>There is somebody else here</item>	<item>PARTY!! Let's make a party</item>	<item>Any ideas what we can do?</item>	<item>Ahh! I'm bored</item>	<item>We need more friends?</item>	<item>Is there any mod on-line?</item>	<item>Hang up and drive</item>	<item>Out of my mind! Back in five minutes</item>	<item>Nothing is impossible for the man who doesn't have to do it himself</item>	<item>If you dance with a grizzly bear, you had better let him lead</item>	<item>When putting cheese in a mousetrap, always leave room for the mouse</item>	<item>When you starve with a tiger, the tiger starves last</item>	<item>BED AND BREAKFAST: Two things the kids will never make for themselves</item>	<item>Man who run in front of car get tired</item>	<item>Man who run behind car get exhausted</item>	<item>Laugh and the world laughs with you</item>	<item>Never put off to tomorrow what you can avoid altogether</item>	<item>An ostrich's eye is bigger than its brain</item>	<item>Every minute in the U.S. six people turn 17</item>	<item>95% of the creatures on earth are smaller than a chicken egg</item>	<item>63% of pet owners sleep with their pets</item>	<item>58% of school kids say pizza is their favorite cafeteria food</item>	<item>One in three dog owners say they have talked to their pets on the phone</item>	<item>One in seven Americans can't locate the U.S. on a map</item>	<item>When you sneeze, all your bodily functions stop, even your heart</item>	<item>I am so clever that sometimes I don't understand a single word of what I am saying</item>	<item>I like to move it, move it</item>	<item>push the button</item>	<item>I'm ok!</item>	<item>Play!Play!Play!</item>	<item>No act of kindness, no matter how small, is ever wasted</item>	<item>To have a good friend is one of the greatest delights of life</item>	<item>Happiness is an unexpected hug</item>	<item>To the world you may be just one person. but to one person you may be the world</item>	<item>To have joy one must share it</item>	<item>It is your friends who make your world</item>	<item>If at first you don't succeed skydiving is not for you</item>	<item>Doing homework is a drag</item>	<item>The pen is mightier than the sword</item>	<item>Good advice is beyond price</item>	<item>Live and learn</item>	<item>Too much knowledge makes the head bald</item>	<item>Knowledge is power</item>	<item>Live and let live</item>	<item>Great deeds live</item>	<item>A sound mind in a sound body</item>	<item>Dry feet, warm head bring safe to bed</item>	<item>Wit is better than wealth</item>	<item>Handsome is as handsome does</item>	<item>A friend's eye is a good mirror</item>	<item>A wise man changes his mind, a fool never will</item>	<item>There is a great force in soft command</item>	<item>A merry heart is a good medicine</item>	<item>Cheek brings Success</item>	<item>Rome was not built in a day</item>	<item>Calamity is a man's true touchstone</item>	<item>Little and sweet</item>	<item>A good name will sell itself</item>	<item>No legacy so rich as honesty</item>	<item>A clean hand wants no washing</item>	<item>Avoid evil and it will avoid you</item>	<item>Return good for evil</item>	<item>Pride goes before a fall</item>	<item>I'm planning to be more spontaneous in the future</item>	<item>I know Karate, Kung Fu, and 47 other dangerous words...</item>	<item>An unbreakable toy is useful for breaking other toys</item>	<item>Keep smiling, it makes people wonder what you're up to</item>	<item>Procrastinate now, don't put it off</item>	<item>Borrow money from pessimists - they don't expect it back</item>	<item>42.7% of all statistics are made up on the spot</item>	<item>A clear conscience is usually the sign of a bad memory</item>	<item>OK, so what's the speed of dark?</item>	<item>Depression is merely anger without enthusiasm</item>	<item>Ambition is a poor excuse for not having enough sense to be lazy</item>	<item>Hard work pays off in the future, laziness pays off now</item>	<item>I intend to live forever -- so far, so good</item>	<item>If at first you don't succeed, destroy all evidence that you tried</item>	<item>I didn't lose my mind, I sold it on e-bay</item>	<item>The Earth Is Full - Go Home</item>	<item>Don't regret doing things, regret getting caught</item>	<item>Is tuna really Chicken?</item>	<item>I did my homework! I just forgot to write it down</item>	<item>Thank you for visiting reality, come again</item>	<item>I can see clearly now, the brain is gone</item>	<item>Ever stop to think, and forget to start again?</item>	<item>A conclusion is simply the place where you got tired of thinking</item>	<item>Don't be so open-minded your brains fall out</item>	<item>Computers are not intelligent. They only think they are</item>	<item>Press any key to continue or any other key to quit...</item>	<item>If at first you don't succeed skydiving is not for you</item>	<item>Every morning is the dawn of a new error...</item>	<item>If one synchronized swimmer drowns, do the rest have to drown too?</item>	<item>If things get any worse, I'll have to ask you to stop helping me</item>	<item>Car service: If it ain't broke, we'll break it</item>	<item>Shin: A device for finding furniture in the dark</item>	<item>Computers make very fast, very accurate mistakes</item>	<item>My software never has bugs. It just develops random features</item>	<item>Disinformation is not as good as datinformation</item>	<item>I like chobots, but I don't think I could eat a whole one</item>	<item>I know Karate, Kung Fu, and 47 other dangerous words...</item></messages>